<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Duck39</title>
    <link>https://duck39.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Duck39</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.144.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 15:01:12 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://duck39.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Copayment insight</title>
      <link>https://duck39.com/posts/test03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 15:01:12 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duck39.com/posts/test03/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My Insight
Copayment in Thailand is a game-changer for expats and locals buying private insurance. It’s a practical way to keep premiums down—vital in a country where private healthcare is world-class but pricey (e.g., a Bangkok hospital MRI might cost ฿20,000+). However, it’s a double-edged sword: a 20% copay on a ฿500,000 cancer treatment is ฿100,000 out of pocket, which could hit hard. If you’re considering it, weigh your health needs and financial cushion. For expats, pairing a copay plan with Thailand’s excellent public system (if eligible via work) might be a smart hybrid approach.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto King’s X Prediction Ignites Firestorm: $1M Bitcoin by 2030?</title>
      <link>https://duck39.com/posts/test02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 15:00:53 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duck39.com/posts/test02/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When @CryptoKing88 tweeted yesterday, “Bitcoin will hit $1M by 2030—mark my words,” the crypto corners of X exploded. The self-proclaimed “Blockchain Prophet” isn’t new to bold calls, but this one—dropped casually on March 1, 2025—has traders, skeptics, and meme lords battling it out in a digital free-for-all. Is this a visionary forecast or just another hype grenade?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-tweet-that-lit-the-fuse&#34;&gt;The Tweet That Lit the Fuse&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s the exact post from @CryptoKing88, timestamped 3:14 PM yesterday:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kafaak copayment</title>
      <link>https://duck39.com/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 14:30:14 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duck39.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;kafaaks-tweet-sparks-debate-on-tech-trends&#34;&gt;Kafaak&amp;rsquo;s Tweet Sparks Debate on Tech Trends&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a recent tweet, &lt;a href=&#34;https://x.com/kafaak&#34;&gt;@Kafaak&lt;/a&gt;, a well-known tech influencer, sparked a conversation about the latest social media trends. The tweet, which read:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The future of social media is all about authentic connections over algorithmic engagement. #TechTrends&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;has generated thousands of replies, with users discussing the shift from engagement metrics to real relationships in the online world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tweet comes at a time when users are questioning social media algorithms. In a world dominated by likes and shares, many are wondering if authentic engagement could be the new measure of success.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
